运气如何
Any luck?
我们怎么知道这菇有没有毒
How do we tell if they're poison?
我只知道一种保险的方法
Uh, there's only one sure way I know of.
等肖恩回来了问他吗
Ask Shane when he gets back?
没错　回答正确
Yeah, you've got it.
谢了
Thank you.
戴尔　我出去一次
Dale, I'm heading out.
宝贝　别走出戴尔的视线　好吗
Sweetheart, I want you to stay where Dale can see you, okay?
好的　妈妈
Yes, mom.
你也是　别走太远了
You too. Don't wander too far.
走得太远就听不到喊声了
Stay within shouting distance.
你要是看到了什么就大吼　我们很快就到
And if you see anything, holler. I'll come running.
明白　老妈子
Yes, mom.
你吓死我了
You scared the hell out of me.
我等了这么久　得有点补偿吧
I bet. That's what you get for keeping me waiting.
我会尽量小声点
I was trying to be quiet.
- 你去哪儿了　-艾米去采蘑菇了
- Where you been? - Amy the mushroom queen…
我得等她回来才能过来
I had to wait for her to get back.
- 我们有多少时间　-够多了
- How much time do we have? - Enough.
- 过来　-好
- Come here. - Okay.
《行尸走肉》
喂　你还活着吗
Hey, are you alive in there?
- 喂喂　-终于出声了
- Hello? Hello? - There you are.
让我一阵好等
You had me wondering.
你在哪里　坦克外面吗
Where are you? Outside?
你现在能看到我吗
Can you see me right now?
对　我可以
Yeah, I can see you.
坏消息是　你被行尸包围了
You're surrounded by walkers. That's the bad news.
那好消息呢
There's good news?
- 没有好消息　-听着　不管你是谁
- No. - Listen, whoever you are,
我要告诉你　我在这里真的很不爽
I don't mind telling you I'm a little concerned in here.
伙计　你真该从我这看看
Oh man. You should see it from over here.
你准会吓瘫掉
You'd be having a major freak-out.
有什么好建议给我吗
Got any advice for me?
有啊　你得逃出去
Yeah, I'd say make a run for it.
“逃出去”　就这些吗
That's it? "Make a run for it"?
别一副不敢相信的样子
My way's not as dumb as it sounds.
要是你从我的角度看过去
You've got eyes on the outside here.
就会看到只有一只行尸还在上面
There's one geek still up.
其他都爬到坦克下面
on the tank but the others have climbed down.
啃那顿马肉大餐去了
and joined the feeding frenzy where the horse went down.
- 听明白吗　-明白
- With me so far? - So far.
坦克另一边的街上没那么多行尸
Okay, the street on the other side of the tank is less crowded.
趁他们不注意赶紧跑　你还有戏
If you move now while they're distracted, you stand a chance.
- 有弹药吗　-都丢在那个口袋里了
- Got ammo? - In that duffel bag I dropped out there,
还有枪　我能拿回来吗
And guns. Can I get to it?
别管那袋子了　想也别想
Forget the bag, okay? It's not an option.
- 你身上有什么武器　-等下
- What do you have on you? - Hang on.
好吧
Yeah. Yeah.
我找到把贝雷塔手枪　一个弹匣
I've got a beretta with one clip,
- 15发子弹　-省着点用
- 15 rounds. - Make 'em count.
跳到坦克的右侧
Jump off the right side of the tank,
一直沿着那个方向跑
keep going in that direction.
跑个大概50码会看到有条小路
There's an alley up the street, maybe 50 yards.
那里会合
Be there.
你叫什么
Hey, what's your name?
你有没有在听　时间紧迫
Have you been listening? You're running out of time.
好吧
Right.
喂　我是活人
Whoa! Not dead!
快点　快跑
Come on! Come on!
这里
Back here!
快来
Come on! Come on!
你干毛呢　快上来
What are you doing?! Come on!
快来　爬上去
Come on, get up.
真犀利啊　伊斯特伍德（美国硬派影星）
Nice moves there, Clint Eastwood.
你个新治安官骑着马过来清理治安吗
You the new sheriff come riding in to clean up the town?
- 那可不是我的目的　-好吧　随你了
- It wasn't my intention. - Yeah, whatever. Yeehaw.
你还真是个傻瓜
You're still a dumbass.
我叫瑞克　谢谢你
Rick. Thanks.
我叫格伦　不用谢
Glenn. You're welcome.
不是吧
Oh no.
好消息是
The bright side:
要是死了　好歹是摔死的
It'll be the fall that kills us.
我这人比较乐天
I'm a glass-half-full kind of guy.
是你在巷子里设了路障吗
Are you the one that barricaded the alley?
别人设的　应该是在行尸占领这里之前
Somebody did… I guess when the city got overrun.
设路障的人肯定没想到会有这么多行尸
Whoever did it was thinking not many geeks would get through.
我在坦克里时　你为什么要冒险帮我
Back at the tank, why'd you stick your neck out for me?
抱着一种天真愚蠢的希望吧
Call it foolish, naive hope.
换作是我在里面
that if I'm ever that far up shit creek,
也希望有人来救我
somebody might do the same for me.
说不定我会比你更白痴
Guess I'm an even bigger dumbass than you.
我回来了　带回一个人外加四个行尸
I'm back. Got a guest plus four geeks in the alley.
快进去
Let's go!
莫拉莱斯　撤
Morales, let's go!
你他妈的　老子真想毙了你
You son of a bitch. We ought to kill you.
淡定　安德莉亚　 放下枪
Just chill out, Andrea. Back off.
拜托　别激动
Come on, ease up.
别激动　你搞毛
Ease up? You're kidding me, right?
这傻逼害死我们了
We're dead because of this stupid asshole.
安德莉亚　我说快他妈把枪放下
Andrea, I said back the hell off.
行　你就开枪吧
Well, pull the trigger.
我们死定了
We're dead… all of us…
拜你所赐
Because of you.
我不明白
I don't understand.
我们来这里找点必需品
Look, we came into the city to scavenge supplies.
你知道怎么才能找吗　得活着
You know what the key to scavenging is? Surviving!
知道怎么才能活着吗　得低调行事
You know the key to surviving? Sneaking in and out, tiptoeing.
这么大张旗鼓地开枪　你以为是决战犹马镇吗
Not shooting up the streets like it's the O.K.Corral.
辟里啪啦的那些行尸大老远都听到了
Every geek for miles around heard you popping off rounds.
你简直就是给他们敲钟开餐
You just rang the dinner bell.
现在明白了吗
Get the picture now?
天呐
Oh god.
话说　你到底在外面干什么
What the hell were you doing out there anyway?
我想引起直升机的注意
Trying to flag the helicopter.
直升机　靠　太扯淡了
Helicopter? Man, that's crap.
- 妈的哪来的直升机　-你丫的是
- Ain't no damn helicopter. - You were chasing a hallucination,
- 产生幻觉了吧　-我的确看见了
- imagining things. It happens. - I saw it.
T仔　呼叫看看　看能联系上其他人吗
Hey, T-dog, try that C.B. Can you contact the others?
其他人　避难所的人吗
Others? The refugee center?
是啊　还避难所呢
Yeah, the refugee center.
你是不是还指望有美味佳肴等着我们
They've got biscuits waiting at the oven for us.
没有信号　上楼顶试试
Got no signal. Maybe the roof.
靠　是迪克森干的吗
Oh no. Is that Dixon?
- 这疯子在干什么　-快快　快走
- What is that maniac doing? - Come on, let's go.
喂　迪克森　你疯了吗
Hey, dixon, are you crazy?!
我的天哪
Oh Jeez.
我说　跟操着家伙的人说话是不是该客气点
Hey! Y'all be more polite to a man with a gun!
这都不懂
Only common sense.
靠　子弹都快没了　你还浪费
Man, you wasting bullets we ain't even got!
是不是想多招点行尸才好啊
And you're bringing even more of them down on our ass!
你给我悠着点
Man, just chill.
整天被墨西哥衰人嚷嚷也好不到哪去
Bad enough I've got this taco-bender on my ass all day.
我要听你嚷嚷吗
Now I'm gonna take orders from you?
没门　伙计　怎么可能
I don't think so, bro. That'll be the day.
“怎么可能”　对我有意见你就说啊
"That'll be the day"? You got something you want to tell me?
- 嘿　T仔　算了　-不行
- Hey, T-dog man, just leave it. - No.
- 算了　没必要
- All right? It ain't worth it.
莫尔　你消停了好吧
Now Merle, just relax, okay?
我们麻烦够多了
We've got enough trouble.
- 你想知道我有什么意见　-对
- You want to know the day? - Yeah.
那我就直说了　吆喝先生
I'll tell you the day, Mr."Yo."
哥不想听黑鬼吆喝
It's the day I take orders from a nigger.
- 狗日的　-莫尔　算了
- Motherfucker! - Hey, come on, Merle. That's enough.
算了
Come on.
迪克森
Dixon!
我靠　别打了
Whoa, cut it out, man!
住手　迪克森　住手
Stop it! Dixon, get off him!
迪克森　你会打伤他的
Dixon, you're gonna hurt him.
莫尔　别闹了
Merle, cut it out!
不要啊　求你了
No no no, please. Please.
行啊　好说
Yeah! All right!
咱们就来开个小会
We're gonna have ourselves a little powwow, huh?
来决定谁当老大
Talk about who's in charge.
我投我自己　你们呢
I vote me. Anybody else?
丫们也来搞点民主
Huh? Democracy time, y'all.
投票的举手啊
Show of hands, huh?
大家都同意吗
All in favor? Huh?
快点啊　投票
Come on. Let's see 'em.
快点
Oh, come on.
都同意吗
All in favor?
可以　很好
Yeah. That's good.
现在我说了算　没错吧
Now that means I'm the boss, right?
还有谁有异议
Yeah. Anybody else?
- 谁有异议　-我
- Hmm? Anybody?　- Yeah.
- 你他妈的是谁啊　-友好的警官
- Who the hell are you, man?!　- Officer friendly.
听着　莫尔　情况变了
Look here, Merle. Things are different now.
不搞种族歧视
There are no niggers anymore.
也不搞白人优越主义
No dumb-as-shit, inbred white-trash fools either.
我们不过是待宰割的人肉
Only dark meat and white meat.
现在只有活人和行尸之分
There's us and the dead.
只有齐心协力才能活下去
We survive this by pulling together,
- 别搞分裂　-你去死吧
- Not apart.　- Screw you, man.
看来你听话不爱听重点
I can see you make a habit of missing the point.
是吗　那你就再死一次吧
Yeah? Well, screw you twice.
对带着枪的人说话别太嚣张
Ought to be polite to a man with a gun.
给点常识好不
Only common sense.
你不会开枪的　你是个警察
You wouldn't. You're a cop.
现在的我
All I am anymore.
只想找回自己的妻儿
is a man looking for his wife and son.
挡我者死
Anybody that gets in the way of that is gonna lose.
给些时间你好好想想
I'll give you a moment to think about that.
还想尝尝吗
Got some on your nose there.
你要拿我怎么样
What are you gonna do?
逮捕我吗
Arrest me?
你搞什么　那是我的私人财产
Hey! What are you doing? Man, that was my stuff!
一旦我松绑　你就死定了
If I get loose, you'd better pray…
听到吗　你这头猪
Yeah, you hear me, you pig?!
- 听到没有　-听得到你在瞎喊
- You hear me?!　- Yeah, your voice carries.
听到没有　你这恶心的猪
Do you hear me, you filthy pig?!
你不是亚特兰大的警官
You're not Atlanta P.D.
- 你哪儿来的　-大路的另一头
- Where you from?　- Up the road a ways.
来自大路另一头的友好警官
Well, officer friendly from up the road a ways,
欢迎你来到大城市
welcome to the big city.
天啊　下面就像时代广场一样
My god, it's like Times Square down there.
- 信号怎么样　-就像迪克森的脑袋
- How's that signal?　- Like Dixon's brain…
残得可以
Weak.
- 继续试　-何必呢　他们什么也做不了
- Keep trying.　- Why? There's nothing they can do.
屁用也没有
Not a damn thing.
首要任务是离开这个城市
Got some people outside the city is all.
根本就没有什么避难所　别作梦了
There's no refugee center. That's a pipe dream.
她说的对　我们得靠自己
Then she's right. We're on our own.
我们要自己找出路
It's up to us to find a way out.
祝你好运
Good luck with that.
据我所知　市里这块不太安全
These streets ain't safe in this part of town from what I hear.
对吧　甜心
Ain't that right, sugar tizz?
宝贝儿
Hey, honeybunch,
帮我解开手铐行不
What say you get me out of these cuffs,
我们找个地方然后大干一场
We go off somewhere and bump some uglies?
- 反正都要死了　-还不如让我死
- Gonna die anyway.　- I'd rather.
好吧　我懂了　原来你是硬骨头啊
Rod Muncher. I figured as much.
走大街出去不安全
The streets ain't safe.
这我们都同意
Now there's an understatement.
大街底下呢　走下水道
What about under the streets? The sewers?
等等
Oh man.
格伦　看看那小巷
Hey, Glenn, check the alley.
看看有没有井盖
You see any manhole covers?
没有　一定在满是行尸的大街上
No, must be all out on the street where the geeks are.
不一定　像这样的二十世纪的老建筑
Maybe not. Old building like this built in the '20s…
大型建筑物在负二层都有
Big structures often had drainage tunnels.
防洪用的通往下水道的排水管道
into the sewers in case of flooding down in the subbasements.
- 你怎么知道　-这是我的工作　曾经是
- How do you know that?　- It's my job… was.
我在城市规划办公室工作
I worked in the city zoning office.
是这里吗　你确定吗
This is it? Are you sure?
我以前把这里上下搜了个遍
I really scoped this place out the other times I was here.
这是这栋楼里唯一通往底下的路
It's the only thing in the building that goes down.
但我从没下去过
But I've never gone down it.
谁会想下去啊
Who'd want to, right?
好吧
Oh. Great.
我们跟在你后面
We'll be right behind you.
不行　至少你不行
No, you won't. Not you.
为什么　觉得我不敢吗
Why not me? Think I can't?
不是
I wasn't…
想说什么就说吧
Speak your mind.
到目前为止　我总是独自一人
Look, until now I always came here by myself…
进进出出　拿些东西　都不是问题
In and out, grab a few things… no problem.
我第一次带上一队人马　就整个乱套了
The first time I bring a group… everything goes to hell.
毫无冒犯之意
No offense.
如果你们要我从这洞里下去　没问题
If you want me to go down this gnarly hole, fine…
但得由我说了算
But only if we do it my way.
下面很狭窄
It's tight down there.
如果我遇到了什么　能尽快逃出来
If I run into something and have to get out quick,
我可不想你们跟在后面堵路　害我被杀
I don't want you all jammed up behind me getting me killed.
我只带一个人　你也不行
I'll take one person… not you either.
你有莫尔的枪　我也见识过你的枪法
You've got Merle's gun and I've seen you shoot.
你得在里面把守店门　保护大家
I'd feel better if you were out in that store.
这样我会更放心
watching those doors, covering our ass.
就你还有把枪　所以你该和他一起
And you've got the only other gun, so you should go with him.
你做我策应　杰奎就待这里
You be my wingman. Jacqui stays here.
一有情况就冲下面喊
Something happens, yell down to us,
- 马上把我们弄上来　-好
- get us back up here in a hurry. - Okay.
那好　大家各司其职
Okay, everybody knows their jobs.
靠
Dah!
抱歉　我拿枪指着你
Sorry for the gun in your face.
人害怕时难免会冲动
People do things when they're afraid.
不　那太不应该了
Not that was entirely unjustified.
可你的确陷我们于绝境
You did get us into this.
要是我帮大家逃出去可以弥补吗
If I get us out, would that make up for it?
弥补不了　不过算是个好开始
No, but it'd be a start.
以后得先打开保险
Next time though, take the safety off.
否则开不了枪
It won't shoot otherwise.
自己的枪吗
Is that your gun?
是个礼物　怎么了
It was a gift. Why?
小红点说明保险打开了
Little red dot means it's ready to fire.
也许你要用到它
You may have occasion to use it.
谢谢提醒
Good to know.
有人在吗
Anybody out there?
喂　有人收到吗
Hello? Anybody read?
真希望听到别人的声音
I'm hoping to hear somebody's voice.
因为只有自己的声音太郁闷了
'cause I'm getting sick and tired of hearing mine.
对　不过是我们俩
Yeah, well, that makes two of us.
干嘛不扔了那破无线电
Why don't you knock that crap off?
这让我头疼　小子
You're giving me a headache, boy.
你干嘛不把脑袋坐到屁股底下
Why don't you pull your head out of your ass?
那你的头就不疼了
Maybe your headache will go away.
妈的　还是想点好事吧
Try some positivity for a change. Damn.
我跟你说
I'll tell you what,
你帮我把手铐解开
you get me out of these cuffs.
我一定给你好好当靠山
and I'll be all "Sammy sunshine" positive for you.
看到那边工具箱里的钢锯了吗
Hey, see that hacksaw over there in that toolbag?
帮我拿过来怎么样　肯定有你好处
Get it for me, hmm? Make it worth your while.
怎么样伙计　快点吧
What do you say, man? Come on.
帮我弄掉这铐子
Get me out of these things.
然后接着揍我吗
So you can beat my ass again?
要不就是多叫我几声“黑鬼”
Or call me nigger some more?
说什么啊　又不是针对你
Come on now. It wasn't personal.
也就是咱俩意见有点不合罢了
It's just that your kind and my kind ain't meant to mix.
有什么大不了
That's all.
又不是说咱俩就不能合作了
It don't mean we can't… work together,
好好谈谈　只要我们大家能双赢
parley, as long as there's some kind of mutual gain involved.
那么　钢锯的事
So… about that hacksaw…
恐怕你还想让我帮你拿那支步枪吧
I guess you want me to get that rifle over there too.
然后等那警察上来时一枪毙了他
so you can shoot that cop when he comes back up, huh?
看来我们是到污水管道了
Yeah, we've got ourselves a sewer tunnel.
杰奎说的对
Jacqui was right.
这能切开吗
Can we cut through it?
能啊　只要给我个喷灯再来半天时间
If we had a blowtorch and half a day, sure.
戴尔的钢锯肯定没戏
Dale's hacksaw sure as hell won't do it.
看上什么了
See something you like?
不是我　不过有个人肯定喜欢
Not me, but I know someone who would.
我妹妹
My sister.
在有些方面她还像个孩子
She's still such a kid in some ways.
独角兽啊　龙啊
Unicorns, dragons.
她就痴迷那类东西
She's into all that stuff.
说到美人鱼　她最喜欢了
But mermaids, they rule.
她喜欢美人鱼
She loves mermaids.
拿走不就得了
Why not take it?
可有个警察正盯着我呢
There's a cop staring at me.
这算行窃吗
Would it be considered looting?
我认为那些规矩都作废了　你看呢
I don't think those rules apply anymore. Do you?
- 你们在下面发现什么了　-出不去
- What did you find down there? - Not a way out.
我们得找条路
We need to find a way…
马上
and soon.
瞧工地那边
That construction site,
卡车司机总是把钥匙放在一起
those trucks, they always keep keys on hand.
根本没办法穿过那片行尸
You'll never make it past the walkers.
可你帮我从坦克里逃了出去
You got me out of that tank.
是　可他们当时在吃东西　都魂不守舍
Yeah, but they were feeding. They were distracted.
我们能再让它们分神吗
Can we distract them again?
就是　听他的　他什么不知道啊
Right. Listen to him. He's onto something.
还“声东击西”呢　从电影里学的吧
A diversion, like on "Hogan's heroes."
- 拜托　你能消停一下吗　-他们是听声辨物吗
- God. Give it a rest. - They're drawn by sound, right?
对　就像狗　听到动静就跑来了
Right, like dogs. They hear a sound, they come.
- 还有呢　-除了能听到你吗
- What else? - Aside from they hear you?
他们用嗅觉辨认　一旦抓到就立刻吃掉
They see you, smell you and if they catch you, they eat you.
- 他们会分辨我们的气味　-你闻不出来吗
- They can tell us by smell? - Can't you?
他们身上有腐尸味　我们没有　多明显的区别
They smell dead, we don't. It's pretty distinct.
如果坏主意也有奥运会的话
If bad ideas were an Olympic event,
- 这个绝对是金牌得主　-他说的没错
- This would take the gold. - He's right.
快停手　慢慢来考虑清楚　好吗
Just stop, okay? Take some time to think this through.
要多慢　他们已经穿过第一道门了
How much time? They already got through one set of doors,
这玻璃也撑不了多久
That glass won't hold forever.
韦恩·邓拉普
Wayne Dunlap.
佐治亚州人
Georgia license.
1979年出生
Born in 1979.
去世时身上有28美元
He had $28 in his pocket when he died…
和一个女生的照片　她很漂亮
and a picture of a pretty girl.
“爱你的蕾切尔赠”
"With love, from Rachel."
他曾像我们一样
He used to be like us…
为账单和房租发愁
worrying about bills.
或者超级杯橄榄球联赛
or the rent or the Super Bowl.
如果我能与家人团聚　一定向他们说起韦恩
If I ever find my family, I'm gonna tell them about Wayne.
还有一件事
One more thing…
他曾是名器官捐赠者
he was an organ donor.
圣母玛利亚
Madre de dios!
上帝
Oh! God!
太恶心了
Gack!
上帝啊
Oh God.
神啊
Dios!
天呐
Oh god.
继续砍
Keep chopping.
- 快吐了我　-等会再吐
- I am so gonna hurl. - Later.
大家手套都戴好了吗
Everybody got gloves?
千万别弄到皮肤上或眼睛里
Don't get any on your skin or in your eyes.
上帝
Oh god!
天呐　太糟了
Oh jeez. Oh, this is bad.
糟的不能再糟了
This is really bad.
想想别的事
Think about something else…
小狗小猫的
puppies and kittens.
死狗死猫还差不多
Dead puppies and kittens.
太不厚道了　你怎么回事
That is just evil. What is wrong with you?
下一次让那疯子好好修理修理他
Next time let the cracker beat his ass.
- 对不起了　-你个混蛋
- I'm sorry, yo. - You suck.
- 跟他们味道一样了吗　-能不一样吗
- Do we smell like them? - Oh yeah.
格伦
Glenn.
以防万一吧
Just in case.
如果我们回得来　你们要准备好
If we make it back, be ready.
那莫尔·迪克森怎么办
What about Merle Dixon?
把斧子给我
Give me the axe.
- 得多弄点内脏　-天啊
- We need… we need more guts. - Oh god!
怎么回事　伙计
Hey, what's happening, man?
T仔　试试那个民用电台
Hey, T-dog, try that C.B.
拜托　你们倒是跟我说句话啊
Hey, come on. Talk to me, y'all.
呼叫大本营　我是T仔　有人收到吗
Base camp, this is T-dog. Anybody hear me?
有人能收到我的信息吗
Can anybody out there hear me?
那里
There.
那混蛋带着手铐钥匙走了吗
That asshole is out on the street with the handcuff keys?
伙计　软管不够长啊
Boy, that hose isn't long for this world, is it?
是不够　先生
No sir.
到底哪里能他妈的给换一个
Where the hell are we gonna find a replacement?
天色很晚了　他们应该回来了才对
It's late. They should've been back by now.
担心也没用
Worrying won't make it better.
干得好　就这样
Attaboy. Yeah.
三二一　拉出来
And three, two, one… pull it.
再来一次
Start it over.
这样做“P”字　绕着手指来
Make your "P" the other way… around your finger.
很好　像缠在手指上一样绑起来
Good, just tie it like around your finger.
好样的
Attaboy.
呼叫大本营
Hello, base camp!
有人能收到信息吗
Can anybody out there hear me?
大本营　我是T仔　有人收到吗
Base camp, this is T-dog. Anybody hear me?
喂　你好
Hello? Hello?
这边信号不太好
Reception's bad on this end.
- 请重复　请重复　-肖恩　是你吗
- Repeat. Repeat. - Shane, is that you?
是他们吗
Is that them?
我们有麻烦了
We're in some deep shit.
我们被困在百货公司里了
We're trapped in the department store.
- 他说他们被困住了　-这到处都是怪物
- He say they're trapped? - There are geeks all over the place.
有成百上千个　我们被包围了
Hundreds of 'em. We're surrounded.
T仔　请重复最后一句　重复下
T-dog, repeat that last. Repeat.
他刚说的是百货商店
He said the department store.
我也听见了
I heard it too.
- 肖恩　-不行
- Shane? - No way.
我们不能去找他们
We do not go after them.
不能让剩下的成员冒险
We do not risk the rest of the group.
- 你们也知道　-就这么撒手不管了吗
- Y'all know that. - So we're just gonna leave her there?
艾米　我知道这很难接受…
Look, Amy, I know that this is not easy…
为了我们大家
She volunteered to go.
她自告奋勇前往城里
to help the rest of us.
没错　但她知道其中的风险吧
I know, and she knew the risks, right?
要是她被困住　那么就死定了
See, if she's trapped, she's gone.
我们得接受事实
So we just have to deal with that.
我们无能为力
There's nothing we can do.
她是我亲姐姐　你个狗娘养的
She's my sister, you son of a bitch.
艾米
Amy…
没事　别担心　小鬼
Come on. It's all right, buddy.
居然行得通　真不敢相信
It's gonna work. I can't believe it.
别说话　继续装
Don't draw attention.
天哪
Oh man.
只是场暴雨而已
It's just a cloudburst.
这里常会下暴雨　很快就会停
We get them all the time. It'll pass real quick.
行尸味是不是被雨水冲掉了
The smell's washing off, isn't it?
- 是不是被冲掉了　-没有
- Is it washing off? - No, it's not.
也许吧
Well, maybe.
快跑
Run!
快快快
Come on, come on, come on.
瑞克
Rick!
快　快开车
Go go go go!
- 他们要丢下我们　-什么
- They're leaving us. - What? What?
- 他们要去哪　-不不　给我回来
- Where they going? Where they going? - No no, come back.
天哪天哪　他们全聚集在那儿
Oh my god. Oh my god. They're all over that place.
你得设法把他们引开
You need to draw them away.
那个商店的前卷帘门那里
Those roll-up doors at the front of the store…
你得帮我把他们从那里引开
That area? …That's what I need cleared.
通知他们　让他们到卷帘门口等着
Raise your friends. Tell them to get down there and be ready.
我要怎么引开这些怪物　我刚没注意听
And I'm drawing the geeks away how? I… I missed that part.
制造噪音
Noise.
到商店的前卷帘门那里去
Those roll-up doors at the front of the store.
就街对面的卷帘门　在那儿会合
facing the street… meet us there and be ready.
快　咱们走　快点
Come on! Let's go, let's go!
等等　你们不能丢下我
Hey, you can't leave me here!
我又不蠢　兄弟　莫拉莱斯
I'm not fooling, man! Morales!
- 哥们　别丢下我　-快点
- Hey, man! Don't do this! - Come on.
那是我的枪　你不能丢下我
Hey, that's my gun. You can't leave me.
你们不要丢下我
Don't leave me here, you guys.
莫拉莱斯　快点
Morales, come on.
来了　我们真得走了
I'm coming! We've gotta go!
莫拉莱斯　你把手铐给我解开　哥们
Morales! You can't leave me like this, man!
T仔　哥们　你不能丢下我不管
Hey, T-dog. No, man. You can't leave me, man.
你不能丢下我　至少把手铐解开
You can't leave me here… not like this.
你会遭天谴的　你还有没有人性
You can't, man. It's not human.
求你了　不要丢下我
Come on, don't do this.
求你了　T仔　行行好
Come on, T. Come on!
快过来　就是这样
Come on, yeah! Yeah!
过来　对　快点过来　好哥们
Come on! Co… that's it! Yes! Come on, baby!
快来
Come on.
快走
Go.
你个狗杂种　你他妈故意的
Son of a bitch! You did that on purpose!
我不是故意的
I didn't mean to!
骗死人呢你　你他妈就是故意的
You lie! You did it on purpose!
- 真的是意外　-别丢下我
- It was an accident! - Don't leave me, man!
别丢下我　不要丢下我
Don't leave me! Don't leave me!
对不起
I'm sorry.
- 你个骗子　-对不起了　兄弟
- You liar! - I'm sorry. Man, I'm sorry.
- 对不起　-别丢下我　别这么做
- I'm sorry.　- Don't leave me! don't do it, man!
操你们全家
Damn you all!
兄弟　别丢下我
Don't leave me, man!
别丢…　别丢下我
Don't leave… don't leave me!
别锁门　你还是不是人
Hey! What are you doing, man?
你会遭报应的
You're gonna rot in hell!
下地狱吧你
- 给我回来　-等我一下
- Come back, man! - Wait a minute!
我来了　别丢下我
Here I come! Don't leave me!
等我啊
Don't leave!
嘘
Shh.
怎么了
What is that?
过来吧　来吧
Come on. Come on.
靠近点　靠近点　来吧来吧
Get closer. Get closer. Come on. Come on.
等等我
Hey, wait for me!
他们进来了　快走　他们来了
They're here! Let's go! They're in here!
- 快走　-快开门
- Let's go! - Open the door!
- 赶紧走　-快
- We've gotta go! - Go!
我进来了
I'm in!
不要丢下我
Don't leave me!
你会下地狱的　去死吧　他妈的
You'll die! Go to hell! Damn you!
你会下第十八层地狱
You're gonna rot in hell!
我居然把钥匙掉了
I dropped the damn key.
格伦人呢
Where's Glenn?